Twilight Sparkle, my most faithful
student. Thank you for coming on such
short notice.
>> Of course, Princess, you said it was
like super urgent, which usually means
mommy wants wipes. Do you need me to
wipe your fat poopy butt?
>> Yes, Twilight. It is apocalyptically
urgent, but it's not butt stuff.
>> Okay, Star Swirl the bearded is here.
Wasn't he mortally wounded by Starlight
Glimmer?
>> We've decided not to focus on that. Ah,
so this is your faithful student,
Princess Celestia. She is indeed very
sexy with that bowl cut. It would be
really funny if she took a dump down my
throat.
>> Starlight Glimmer has stolen Star Swirl,
the bearded ancient magic staff, and her
having that staff puts the entire
universe at risk.
>> Star Swirl lost to Starlight Glimmer.
>> I didn't lose you, black [__] SHE
FARTED IN MY FACE and disoriented me. IT
WASN'T A FAIR AND HONORABLE FIGHT.
>> You lost Star Swirl. Grow up.
>> Today is the day of the solar eclipse
because my staff was forged from a
fallen star that crashed in my bathroom
while I was taking a big poopy and
watching a Bartleby X Sonic the Hedgehog
music video on my Android phone. Bartle
is so cool. while completely butt naked
except for my hat that cost me 42 whole
dollars.
>> Oh [__]
>> It is directly bound to the very essence
of magic itself. At noon, a spire will
erupt from the earth as it does every
1,081
minutes. Whoever stands at top it with
my magic staff in hooves during totality
will gain limitless power.
>> Then why are you all just sitting here?
Go beat her up and take it back from
her.
>> That's where things become complicated.
You see, Twilight, the grand galloping
gala is in like 12 minutes. Also, I
don't want my chicken nuggies to get
cold.
>> Starlight Glimmer is about to become a
god, and you can't deal with it because
you want to throw a party.
>> Well, I am the host.
>> Don't tell us what to do, you worthless
female.
>> Oh my god, Twilight. I'm I'm sorry. I
didn't mean to. I swear I'm not sexist.
>> Twilight, come back. Please retire
yourself from the meeting Star Swirl. We
don't allow discrimination in this
kingdom unless it's targeted towards
gays, blacks, and the mentally
challenged.
Okay. Who here wants to help me stop
Starlight Glimmer from becoming a
literal god?
>> You mean like today?
>> Today would be preferable. Yes.
Sorry, Twilight. I promised my sisters
I'd go back to the rock farm today and
help liberate it to earn my sisters
their freedom.
>> If we don't stop Starlight today, we
could lose the entire universe.
>> So,
>> so I need you here.
>> I say we go with Pinkie Pie. If Twilight
is choosing to save the universe over
Pinkie Pie's sister, she's basically
saying family is less important than
like space rocks and stuff.
>> Applejack, I don't know if you're
desperate to get a dub on me, but this
is such a weird hill for you to die on.
>> Why did you get vanilla ice cream when
this establishment has 37 options?
>> Vanilla is the most chemically complex
flavor containing over 200 distinct
flavor compounds. You're not going to
get a W today on me, Applejack. Get over
it.
>> Sorry, Twilight. I got to stay home for
a package to make sure it doesn't get
stolen. I bought a new Hot Wheel for my
collection.
>> Oh, yeah. I forgot you're autistic.
>> And I just don't want to.
>> Oh, yeah. I forgot you're a [__]
Sounds like Starlight is going to try
something crazy again today. Don't get
involved in her mess. Okay.
>> Why not? because you're omnipotent and
I'd rather finish this in a way that
doesn't involve blowing those two up.
You think I'm omnipotent?
>> Mary, you're a late baby.
>> You knew I was coming?
>> Of course I did. I've got an ancient
cosmic staff. Come sit with me.
>> Want to smoke?
You know I don't do that stuff and you
shouldn't either.
>> Oh, don't be lame.
>> Take one. It tastes better when you're
doing it with somebody else.
I take it you're waiting for the eclipse
to start.
>> Well, duh. I know about the whole Gala
thing, too. And Celestia's cold nugs. It
will be the perfect audience for my
coronation to godhood. I can't wait to
see the look on Twilight's face. She's
my sister now.
>> Don't start. We made the agreement that
you wouldn't get between me and
Twilight, regardless of your
relationship with her, or what I do with
this.
>> Well, I never thought it would get to
this point. This is other worldly magic
starlight.
Not equestrian. It came from a fallen
star. You think I'm not strong enough to
control it?
What if you aren't?
Check it, girls. Barbed wire on the
fence. Graffiti and bullet shells on the
ground. It's like we're back in
Ponyville.
>> Pinky, why is there barbed wire on the
fence? Like I didn't see no animals
walking about besides us ponies with fat
butt cheeks.
>> My sister Limestone kicked down the
first fence. So our parents, they made
it taller. But then she got over that
one, too. So they put barbed wire on
top.
>> That's crazy. Is that them over there by
the window with the crossbow?
>> Yeah.
>> Who's limestone?
>> Fluttershy, do you ever listen to
anything we say?
>> Well, maybe I would if the pink mentally
challenged baby ever said anything worth
listening to.
>> Damn, Fluttershy is spicy today.
>> Anyway, Lindstone is my dear sister.
>> No one cares.
Hey, do you hear that?
>> No.
>> Exactly. That's the sound of how many
people give a [__]
Look, limestone. Marble has been tied to
the whipping tree again.
Do you want to go out and whip her next
or shall I?
>> I want to do it. You got to do it the
last three times.
>> No, I want to do it. Look, Limestone,
beyond the tree where our father and
mother gives us lashes. It's pinky. Our
peas have been heard nationwide and
saviors from foreign lands have come to
free us.
>> Okay, let's go down and greet them
before mom and dad do since they're
racist against every pony on the RGB
color wheel.
I've been to eight county fairs,
wrangled a dozen pigs, and fixed a
fence. But I ain't ever never smelled a
place this caked up in crap. Wow, bet
the smell alone could knock the boots
right off a donkey.
>> Pinky, you have returned. And you have
brought companions of considerable
aptitude. Well done.
>> Did our parents see you? Your parents?
>> Our parents run this rock farm with the
vigilance of falcons guarding a fragile
stone. They do not know. They do not
know that we sisters yearn to see the
world beyond basalt.
>> Ma limestone. Who are these strange
individuals? You didn't tell us you
would be having guests over.
>> They're just passing by, Dad.
>> That's strange. This farm is 10 miles
from anything worth passing by.
>> Well, shoot, sir. Y'all ain't wrong
there, sir. This place is more tucked
away than a pickle jar and Granny
Smith's fat butt. If you're scooping
what I'm pooping,
>> quit your crying. No one loves you
enough to come save you.
Get rid of them quickly. Strangers ask
questions, and questions lead to
attention.
>> Yes, Pops. I'll do as you ask.
>> See that you do for your sister's sake.
>> Who wants pizza?
It's still frozen.
>> It's amazing. Just What is this? That's
a Tatino's party pizza, or what I like
to call the pinnacle of God's creation.
>> Where did you find such a thing?
>> The Dollar Tree right outside your farm.
>> Wow. A store where you can buy things
for just a dollar.
>> Well, now it's 125.
>> Sister, we have to go out there and find
more Tatino's party pizzas.
>> All right, Ma. You said you parked a
tractor we could use to escape.
>> There she is. Our noble steed.
>> That is not a tractor. That is a toy. A
baby toy. A toy for babies. Ma, I'm
getting mad again.
>> Ma, this isn't exactly usable.
>> I'm so confused. It looked significantly
bigger 24 years ago.
>> Well, I'm going home.
>> Applejack, you can't. Not after we've
come so far.
>> Pinkie Pie, you know I love you, but I'm
not getting rocks forcefully shoved up
my butt by your parents for this.
Let's go to sleep, Limestone. The hour
grows late, and if father finds us
wandering in darkness, he will tie us to
the whipping tree and administer the
sacred punishment of 30 lashes. The rest
of you get off our lawn.
>> This is the worst night ever
>> because we failed.
>> No, because for the first time in a long
time, I let myself believe.
>> Limey
Pinkie Pie, cease your weeping. You are
being annoying and I need to be up at 4
in the morning to farm rocks or whatever
the hell it is we do on this farm.
>> Shut up, Ma. She's only crying because
of you.
>> Why don't you come up here and make me,
you big dumb idiot? Or are you just
going to sit there like a rock?
Limestone? What is wrong? You seem
perturbed. Have a Tatino's party pizza.
A gift from the world outside.
You ruined everything.
>> Ruination is but a lens through which
one views unforeseen outcomes.
>> No, Mod. Shut up. Stop talking. You
brought a toy tractor to our grand
escape. All of you keep telling me this,
but I swear it was once large
>> when you were 3 years old.
>> So, you're telling me time alters
perception? I'll remember that next time
when we try to escape again in 20 or so
years.
>> This was our one and only chance to get
off this farm. Pinky brought help.
Marble was ready. I was ready. And you,
you show up with a plastic toy that
can't even hold one pony.
>> Limestone.
I'm trying my best. I'm sorry. I'm just
stupid.
>> I wanted out, Ma, for just one night. I
wanted to believe we could get away.
>> I understand your sorrow truly, for I
too have gazed upon the horizons of
possibility and felt them retreat like a
tide.
>> No, you don't. You've already accepted
this place. You're complacent and I'm
not. You don't really want to leave this
farm because you know you wouldn't
amount to anything out there because
you're fat, bald, and wearing a wig.
Wait, you choose to look like that?
>> That last part may be true, but I am not
complacent. I simply lack the strength
to rebel. You have the fire I lost long
ago.
When I was a fat, ugly baby, I tried to
flee on my own. I climbed over that
dreaded fence with barbed wire that our
mommy and daddy put up to keep us ugly
babies from reaching the world outside
and find happiness. But when I got over,
do you know what the first thing I did
was? I looked back at you, LIMESTONE.
The world felt too large for one little
pony. And the rocks were the only things
that didn't overwhelm me. So, I climbed
back over and pretended like nothing
life-changing had happened.
>> Oh, Ma, why didn't you ever tell me
that? If you did, maybe I would have
went easy on your beatings.
>> You never ask me my opinion on things.
>> I'm sorry. I shouldn't have screamed at
you.
>> It's fine. Your anger is a sign of life.
A sign that you are not as trapped as I.
>> I just want to be free.
>> Then keep wanting it because giving up
is how you become like me.
>> Did you hear that?
>> Yes. Liquid precipitation.
It hasn't rained on the rock farm since
before we were born. It's a sign,
[__] We can use the cover of rain to
escape. Let's make like a fart and blow.
Oh no, it's not actually raining. Dad
just turned on the hose to trick us.
>> Ignous Rockpie, get your crossbow. The
girls are on their 47th escape attempt
this week.
>> I see them.
Direct hit.
>> Damn it. Mod, are you okay?
>> I just got shot in the leg. I'll live.
You must take Marble and run like the
wind.
>> I see you.
>> Take yourself and run like the wind.
>> You're not going anywhere, you stupid
[__]
>> Just run, Lime. You are the fastest,
strongest, and sexiest of us. You can
still reach the fence if you try.
>> No, I'm not leaving you here to remain a
prisoner. You're the one who gave me
hope. I'm afraid the outcome is
statistically likely. Regardless of our
feelings, my sister, you always said you
wanted to leave. Now, is that time?
>> I'm not going anywhere. Not without you
or your fat butt, you crazy [__]
>> Look, there they are at Dollar Tree. I
fear I'll never make it over the fence
with my leg damaged like this. Dear
sister, you must leave me behind.
>> I'm not going to sacrifice you.
>> Then sacrifice yourself for the result
is the same. Throw me sister to freedom
and stay yourself imprisoned on this
farm. It's what you deserve for kind of
being a [__]
>> Well, damn [__] you're right. At least
one of us should be free.
>> Then do your damn job.
Ow. Limestone, help me.
>> Limestone, you made it out out of the
rock farm.
>> You're damn right, little sis. And do
you want to know why? It's because if I
gave up, I'd never see those pink cheeks
again. You gave me the courage because
you were like always the one at the back
of my mind telling me to like, never
give up, and [__]
Oh, limestone.
This is great. Just a totally normal
gala. Most certainly not happening on
the same day as a universe ending
eclipse.
>> Twilight, calm your tits. If you keep
shaking like that, ponies are going to
think I beat you.
>> But you do beat me. Well, stop or I'm
going to beat you.
>> If the universe ends, it ends and there
is little we can do to stop it.
>> Look, [__] I'm just saying
statistically speaking, someone is
probably becoming a god tonight.
>> I most certainly hope it doesn't come to
that. By the way, do you like my dress?
>> Not really. It makes you look like a fat
cupcake. Hey, Twilight, where's the
bathroom? I got to take a big smelly
poop in the toilet before I go dance in
the middle of the room. It's down the
hall, but Star Swirl used all of the
toilet paper rolls to build himself a
new staff. So, don't expect to wipe.
>> That's fine. I don't ever really do that
kind of stuff.
>> Hey, Twilight, quick question about the
uh about the eclipse.
>> Eclipse? What eclipse? You mean the
eclipse happening right now? Holy [__]
>> Oh, yeah. Supernormal. Totally normal.
Just the moon doing moon things,
>> right? Just celestial bodies casually
aligning in a way that historically ends
civilizations.
>> Yeah, except Starsworld staff got
stolen. So, whoever's on the spire
during totality gets all the power in
the universe.
>> A massive structure has emerged from the
>> Wait, go back one. A massive structure
has emerged from the ground
approximately 30 seconds ago. Viewers
may notice this event appears to
coincide with today's previously
scheduled eclipse. Sources have
identified the figure at the summit as
Star Swirl the Bearded Apprentice
Starlight Glimmer, a unicorn previously
involved in several incidents.
Starlight Glimmer, give me back my
stolen [__]
>> I knew you couldn't help but approach
me, fool. Are you sure you want to go
another round with your superior? You
only won because you farted in my face
when I wasn't expecting it. So it
doesn't count.
>> Yeah, it does, [__]
>> No, it doesn't.
>> Does too.
>> No, you did not OVERPOWER ME MAGICALLY.
I DIDN'T LOSE.
>> Face it, Boomer. You didn't come here to
stop me. You came here because you're
embarrassed and you simply can't stand
that I'm better than you.
>> Unfortunately for you, history will not
see it that way. Get on out here, boys.
>> You recruited three random guys from the
Equestria Girls universe as backup.
>> Light her up, sexy teenagers. Kill her
before SHE GETS AWAY AND TELLS EVERYONE
HOW MUCH OF A COWARDLY PISS BABY I AM.
Running away again. You'll never get a
better chance to win back your title of
Equestria's most powerful magician than
this.
We're here at the Grand Galloping Gala.
Star Swirl the Bearded, the hero of us
all. The final hope for Equestria is
currently being ass blasted against the
rock face like a [__] unable to move.
I know we can only struggle to watch as
historic events take place. Is this the
end of life as we know it?
Holy [__]
Cadence move.
>> Damn it.
>> Jinks.
>> Every pony, calm down. Everything is
under control. For now, please find
sanctity in the [__] stained corner of
the ballroom by the loosely hanging
tornado shelter sign and have yourselves
some apple juice and Costco hot dogs.
Sister, our first line of defense has
fallen. Luna, shut up. Twilight and Coco
Palmell, I want the two of you to go up
there and beat up Starlight Glimmer. We
have like 7 seconds left until the
eclipse forms and Starlight Glimmer
blows up the world or some [__]
>> I'm sorry, but why me?
>> You are both lawfully and sexually the
least desirable of us all. So, if
something happens to you, the kingdom
shall easily recover.
>> Koko, we are on a very tight schedule.
I'm trying. It's just so high and scary.
>> You're an olyicorn princess. You have
wings and superpowers. You're not
supposed to be afraid of heights.
>> Hey, Twilight, if we make it out of this
alive, can I be adopted into your
family?
>> Literally, where did this come from?
>> Shining armor is basically like a
brother to me already. I am so confused
why you suddenly think you have ties to
my family. All right, how about this? If
we both make it out alive, you can go
around telling people we're siblings.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. And if anyone asks me, I will
absolutely deny it.
>> It's over, Starlight. Give me the staff.
On the contrary, in only a couple of
moments, the sun and moon will be
perfectly aligned. And when they are, no
unicorn or alicorn will be able to stop
me. That is, unless you can tear this
staff from my very hooves.
It would seem that we are evenly
matched. But you know what that means?
Victory is mine.
>> Literally, what is happening? This will
be a new world built by someone who
knows what it's like to be afraid and
ignored. A world for every mayor who's
afraid to walk the streets at night
under the fear of stallions. Men will be
swallowed by the abyss for they have no
place in paradise.
Freedom.
>> The blight known as alicorns will be
purged. For my will has no need for
thrones because every little pony will
be treated as equals because I say they
are. No more gods and no more kings. My
beautiful world. A world where women
never have to fear again.
I am so confused right now.
Bullies also won't have a place in the
new world.
>> Do you know what androphobia is?
>> Fear of men. I don't get it. I mean, I
nerd
>> understand being uncomfortable around
them but afraid of half the population.
It just sounds a bit silly to me. What's
silly is judging someone for their fear
without getting an understanding of what
gave them that fear in the first place.
>> Mary, what are you? Let go. You're not
helping.
>> Not helping would be letting you go
through with this.
Oh [__]
>> No, no, no. You broke it. You, you
stupid idiot. Whatever. I can still kick
your ass even with half a staff.
>> Which one will you save, Trixie? Your
precious hat or your darling wife?
You're so dumb, Starlight. Trixie may be
dumb as [__] but even she wouldn't. I'm
coming, baby.
You [__] Come along, Mary. This world
is dying. Starlight, wait. The next time
you see me, I'll be the goddess of the
abyss. Give me what's left of the staff.
I'm going down there after her.
>> No. Your way only made things worse. The
only one she'll listen to is me.
>> Mary, you do realize that if you fail,
the universe will die. It's already
gone. Everything was devoured by the
abyss. And Starlight has total control
over it with that staff. But she won't
let it take me.
You have to trust me on this.
Well, this place is aggressively
beautiful. It should be. I modeled it
after you.
Wouldn't it be great if we just didn't
rewrite the world? We can just stay here
forever where we don't have to hide
behind masks, where we can just be
ourselves. That's a shame. If I remember
correctly, you always loved
redecorating. And you always loved
showing up when it's already too late.
The world is gone, Marionette. You say
that like you're proud. Why wouldn't I
be? I'm happy as can be. Everything I
ever hated is gone. This is the best. I
can do anything I want in this place.
Even heal you. Make it as if those
hideous burns never happened.
These scars make me who I am. Why? Why
are you being so persistent? Why don't
you ever listen to me anymore? I'm
offering to remake the world for you. I
don't want some fake life. I want to
live in Trixie's world, and I want to
live in it with you. That's Twilight
talking. The old you would have never
gone against me.
Then put an end to me. It's obvious you
hate this new me so much. If you're not
willing to change, even a little bit to
meet me halfway, as I've done many times
for you, then there truly is no future
for us.
Perhaps you're right. Erasing you will
erase all those nights I wasted staying
up fighting with you.
Erase all those stupid jokes you made
that I still don't understand. And erase
the worst moments of our lives.
but also us surviving them.
I don't know what Twilight did to you,
but you need to let it go. Your hatred
for her is killing you from the inside.
Starlight, hey, what's wrong?
>> You need to choose your words more
carefully. We make the rules here. Call
something a disease in this place and it
starts acting like one.
Starlight, do you love me?
>> No, I don't.
>> Have you ever?
>> No, I loved the attention. I didn't love
you, though.
>> Oh, I see. That's okay. Having a friend
who listen is also important.
>> I don't see you as a friend either.
Then what exactly am I to you?
>> Nothing.
>> That's okay, too. You don't owe me love.
You don't owe anyone anything. I'm still
going to kill everyone.
>> No, you're not. You're exhausted and
you're sick.
>> Go to sleep.
I don't want to stop to hear your lies
to me.
Hold me now. Look out the world around
you.
I'll always be waiting for you.
Don't you say goodbye. Say goodbye
forever. I don't want to hear anymore.
Don't you say goodbye. Let me leave.
Kiss me like you did it before. Don't
you say
goodbye.
The world around you.
Get away from my sister.
>> You say goodbye. Say goodbye. I don't
want to hear anymore.
Don't you say goodbye. Let me leave me
never
more. Don't you say goodbye. Say goodbye
forever. I don't want to cry anymore.
Don't you say goodbye. Heat.
Heat.
Marionette, thanks to your selfless
actions today, the universe still
stands.
>> Our world was spared collapse because
you chose love and compassion to be your
ally.
>> For such deeds, we offer you the
greatest gift of all. Take your rightful
place as an ollicorn and live beyond the
limits of a single lifetime.
>> Thank you, princess, but I don't think I
can accept that offer.
>> I'm afraid agreeing to those terms would
one day result in me standing over the
graves of the ones I care about. And
that scares me more than dying ever
could. So, if it's okay, I want to live
the rest of my life as I am now. I don't
wish for a life where I have to watch
the ponies I love die.
Can she do that?
>> I don't know. No one's ever really said
no before.
Starlight Glimmer, please step forward.
It is time to decide what your
punishment will be.
>> Burn the witch.
>> Well, well, well. If it ain't about damn
time, justice is finally going to be
served on this [__] Why, this just
might be the best day of my life.
>> Princess, please go easy on her.
>> Shut the hell up. I understand that she
is your gay little pooky bear, but
nevertheless, she is obviously a mare of
pure evil. Sunset Shimmer. For what you
did, you will be
>> Sunset Shimmer.
>> What? Why? Why did you say that name?
>> You just called me Sunset Shimmer.
>> What? No. No, I didn't.
>> I'm pretty sure you did.
>> Oh my god. I did it again, didn't I? I'm
such a fool.
Why won't you leave me alone?
A
>> Starlight Glimmer for erasing half of
Pony kind, plunging everything into an
eternal abyss, and attempting to become
a god. Your punishment is two days of
community service.
>> What? Two measly days. You have got to
be pooping on my butt. That girl is a
monster. SHE'S HOLDING A GUN RIGHT NOW.
I demand to see some pony punished for
what SHE DID TO ME. YEAH,
>> I'm afraid the stupid ass [__] is
right, dumbass. There is still a much
harsher punishment that needs to be
dealt in this [__] before we consider
our job here to be done and proceed to
go home and log into various chat rooms
to hang out with underageed boys.
>> Very well.
Starsw Swirl the bearded, would you step
forward, please?
>> What? What is the meaning of
>> Star Swirl the Bearded? You are
sentenced to 10 years in the federal
prison for the war crime of kidnapping
of three humans from the Equestria Girls
universe to use as canon fodder in your
own personal dispute with Starlight.
Plus five more years for twerking here
in the royal throne room.
>> I am Star Swirl the bearded ark mage of
a thousand ages. I can shake my goods
whoever I damn well please. This is a
travesty. A mockery of justice most
foul. You can't give her the win.
>> Oh, put a sock in it.
>> Silence. Wrench of the void. I will not
be humiliated by a sorceress who used
such crude means to obtain victory.
Dear Princess Celestia,
>> today I learned a very important lesson
about family and about myself that makes
me even happier than when I think about
good boobies.
>> Whether it's journeying to the depths of
the earth or simply needing help to
climb over a fence that's a little too
high, there's no place a girl wouldn't
go to save her sister. I also learned
that every girl just wants a place to
belong, a place where she's allowed to
fail and grow.
>> And maybe even a little more if you
catch my drift. Haha. I'll th it all
back anyway. I threw it all back
down a couple feet again to catch the
wind that still remains. But I'm left
breathless anyway. I thought the world
>> I was able to give Marionette a space
like that
>> and I watched her become someone new
because of it
>> again.
>> Starlight never had that sort of place.
I don't think I can be the one to give
it to her. There's too much history
between us. Too many wounds that still
ache when we look at each other.
But I think there is someone
who might be able to.
She pretends to not enjoy the company.
But I'm pretty sure she's lying. After
all, sometimes it's the ponies who are
broken in similar ways who can reach
another when no one else can.
Can't be the end.
This can't be the end.
>> It says, "You always taught me." One act
of kindness sparks another. And even
after everything Starlight has done, I
still believe there's a small light at
the end of her tunnel as well.
>> I hope I'm right.
>> Come to bed, fatty. I want to feed you
chocolate cake and rub your belly fat
until you fart. Just finishing up, dear.
Hurry up. Your faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle.
>> Hurry up.
>> Hi there. I'm Pinkie Pie and I just got
done taking a major dump. Don't forget
to like, comment, and subscribe. And if
you want to see me free the rest of my
sisters from eternal servitude on the
rock farm someday, please help support
my cause by signing up to join Tamers 1
2 3 4 5's Patreon so that one day he can
make a followup or some [__] If you do,
you get some really cool prizes like
this highquality transparent gift of my
sister being tied to a tree and
rightfully punished, as well as various
other gifts from previous episodes, like
that one episode that was banned from
YouTube a few months ago for being too
sexy. Bye-bye.
I'm crazy about you, but I am. It's just
the way you make me feel. But you keep
running every I touch my hand. So baby
I'll be there.
Yeah.
Heat.
Why don't you let me
show me how
you say
you
Don't know why I'm crazy about you, but
I am. It's just the way you make me
feel.
But you keep running every time you
touch my hand. The baby was the deal.